Hi, I'm Gretchen Rivas with Relax To The Max Massage Therapy.
And today we're going to talk about, how to find a massage therapist.
If you are in town visiting, one of the things you can do is, you can look on-line, or you can also look in the yellow pages, and call one of those adds.
Now if you're in town and you just decided to try massage therapy for the first time, one of the best resources is of course, people that you know and referrals.
So I would ask your friends and family if they ever received massage, and if they did, if they liked it, and who they used, and that's the best way to go.
Another way you can go is, amtamassage.org is for the American Massage Therapy Association, they have a list of all their professionals on-line, and they're certified and registered massage therapist, so that's the safe way to go.
When you do find somebody you want, ask them some questions, find out how long they've been licensed, how long they've been practicing, and what type of massage therapy that they do, to make sure that they can meet your massage needs.
And then ask them any other questions that you might have.
And when you go to visit them, if you're not comfortable, you do have the right to speak up and say something, and also to terminate the massage at anytime, so don't forget that, if the massage therapist goes to deep, or you don't like the work, you do have the right to say no.
But in general, massage is a very enjoyable experience, and it should be.
And so, this is how you would look and find a massage therapist.